this code we've been given raises an
error and we need to determine why we
get this error
and fix it so let's run our code and
just see
the error it's a syntax error that has
been raised
ruby's telling us that it was expecting
the keyword
end so let's look back at our code
you can see that we only have one
keyword end in our code on line
six however ruby is expecting an
end for both the if statement and our
method definition
so this end on line six gets matched as
part of our if statement
the reason an error is being raised is
that there is no
end associated with our method
definition
so we can correct this error by adding
the keyword end on line seven
now when we run our code it runs without
error
you